JO TROTECHAUD

Information Sys. and Tech. Student

(909) 735-0152



jotrotechaud@protonmail.com



362 Flordason Dr. Calimesa, CA



shuddfouei.github.io



SUMMARY

Hi! I'm Jo Trotechaud, an IST undergraduate pursuing cybersecurity, with an associates degree in Computer Science as well as half a decade of customer service experience. I'm seeking a position in the field of IT/IS with goals to become a security or business analyst.

EDUCATION

Cal State University, San Bernardino

Information Systems and Technology - Cybersecurity concentration

2023 - Present

Crafton Hills College

Associates Degree in Computer Science 2020-2023

SKILLS

- Communication and interpersonal skills
- MySQL, MariaDB
- Python
- C++
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Shell/CLI
- Linux Configuration
- Networking

CERTIFICATIONS

- Associates Degree in Computer Science
- AWS Fundamentals

WORK EXPERIENCE

Team Member - Food Service

Gourmet Pizza Shoppe | 2023 - Present

 Customer service and order fulfillment via phone orders and utilizing the PoS with face to face transactions. This job also encompasses working with a team in a fast-paced environment in an assembly line.

Team Member - Food Service

Jersey Mikes | 2020-2023

 Charged with training and organizing my coworkers, counting stock, managing online systems to maintain online order organization, and ensuring positive customer service experiences.

Courtesy Clerk

Stater Bros. Markets | 2021 - 2022

- Worked to ensure quality experience and customer satisfaction
- Physically aided customers with loading groceries
- Helped customers in finding products